[{"id":213,"question":"Words ORDER BY in the SQL operator","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"eliminates all repeated rows from the result set","answer_b":"allows you to combine the results of individual queries across multiple tables into a single result table","answer_c":"converts the value of a column or function to a different type","answer_d":"changes the order of output rows","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":351,"question":"What is a composite key?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"its is a key that is defined as the primary key in another table","answer_b":"it is a key that uniquely identifies a record in a database","answer_c":"its is an optional key and allows null values","answer_d":"it is a primary key that consists of more than one field that uniquely identifies a record","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":390,"question":"MySQL supports different Character Sets, which command is used to display all of them?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SHOW;  ;","answer_b":"None Of The Mentioned","answer_c":"CHARACTER SET;","answer_d":"SHOW CHARACTER SET","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":397,"question":"Commands passed to the MySQL daemon are written in","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"English","answer_b":"The Structured Query Language","answer_c":"Your Choice From Perl, PHP, Java Or Some Other Languages","answer_d":"Swedish","answer_e":"Binary","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":241,"question":"Can you start two MySQL servers at one PC?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":329,"question":"How can you change table sctructure after it was created?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CHANGE TABLE","answer_b":"MODIFY TABLE","answer_c":"ALTER TABLE","answer_d":"UPDATE TABLE","answer_e":"It's not possible to change the structure","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":221,"question":"The command to remove rows from a table \"MOVIE\" is:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"REMOVE FROM MOVIE","answer_b":"DROP FROM MOVIE","answer_c":"DELETE FROM MOVIE WHERE","answer_d":"UPDATE FROM MOVIE","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":227,"question":"Which SQL statement is used to extract data from the database?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SELECT","answer_b":"ACCESS","answer_c":"OPEN","answer_d":"GET","answer_e":"ACQUIRE","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":226,"question":"You can add a row using SQL in a database with which of the following?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ADD","answer_b":"CREATE","answer_c":"INSERT","answer_d":"MAKE","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":216,"question":"Which is the right syntax for the DISTINCT SQL statement?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SELECT DIFFERENT col1, col2 FROM table;","answer_b":"SELECT DISTINCT col1, col2 WHERE table;","answer_c":"SELECT DISTINCT col1, col2 FROM table;","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":" Easy"}]